

I am a natural problem solver, **Experienced Web Developer** specializing in front end/backend development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, JAVA, C, Python, JAVA, Django Framework. Strong background in project management, a dedicated researcher and a practitioner.

# **ABDULRAZAK YAHUZA**

#### Phone:

- +2348039099210
- +2348099337676

#### E-Mail:

yahuzaabdulrazak@gmail.com

#### Address:

No 84 Kachia by abuja road rigasa kaduna.

#### Linkedin:

linkedin.com/yahuzaabdulrazak

### **Skill Highlights**

- Dedicated researcher
- Project management
- Problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused
- Microsoft Office package

#### Languages

- English
- Hausa

#### **Hobbies**

- Writing / Reading
- Research
- Coding
- Problem solving
- Tutoring
- Design

# **Experience**

Web Developer

2015 to Date

2018 to Date

**Private Mentorship** 

## **Education**

2016-2020

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science - Ahmadu Bello University, Zaria

2009 - 2014

SSCE: West African Examination Council - Hassana Memorial Schools Kaduna

2002-2008

Primary Education: KDSG (Certificate of Primary Education) - NNPC Staffs Schools Kaduna

#### **Certifications**

**Google Digital Skills for Africa (certificate):** Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

ICIS | CNSS Certified Network Security Expert: ICSI (International Cybersecurity Institute), UK

**CS50x (certificate)**: CS50 Awarded from Cambridge, Massachusetts, Harvard University

#### References

References available on request